{"data":[{"question":"He is not very sanguine about his chances of successful.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"it","b":"hardly","c":"concentration","d":"such","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Hardly-> hard","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"She admires Korean actresses in so far as she wears as them.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"keep","b":"reference","c":"near in","d":"convenience","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Near in-> near \/next to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"We are interested of the conservation of forests.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Put","b":"on","c":"otherwise","d":"would","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Would-> will","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"I think there are any resources that we have left untapped.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"pilots","b":"responsible","c":"for","d":"safe","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Safe-> safty","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"He enrichs his knowledge by listening to the radio every night.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"country","b":"are","c":"moreover","d":"polluted","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"We have searched for some of the books to which you need.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"make","b":"checking","c":"all","d":"after","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- After-> before","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"It is many years for Mount Vesuvius last erupted.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"having","b":"a little","c":"to celebrate","d":"David","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- David-> David's","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Reforming the education system will be a difficulty process.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"old","b":"to be","c":"of","d":"parents","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Enough old-> old enough","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"I keep my reference books near in my desk for convenience.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"he","b":"has","c":"but","d":"was","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Has-> had","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Put the cap back on the bottle, otherwise the juice would spill.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"need","b":"a","c":"to","d":"with","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- With-> on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"}]}